<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Reykunyutsyìp</string>

    <!-- Languages -->
    <string name="german">Deutsch</string>
    <string name="estonian">Eesti</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="navi">Na\'vi</string>
    <string name="french">Français</string>
    <string name="hungarian">Magyar</string>
    <string name="dutch">Nederlands</string>
    <string name="polish">Polski</string>
    <string name="russian">Pусский</string>
    <string name="swedish">Svenska</string>
    <string name="lang_unknown">Unknown</string>

    <!-- UI -->
    <string name="search_description">Search</string>
    <string name="search_box">Search..</string>
    <string name="search_help">Type Na\'vi or your preferred language in the search bar to search</string>

    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="downloading_dict">Downloading dictionary…</string>
    <string name="error">ERROR!</string>

    <string name="results_empty">No results</string>
    <string name="end_of_list">(end)</string>

    <string name="image_copyright">Artwork copyright Eana Unil</string>

    <string name="translate">Translate</string>
    <string name="sentence_analysis">Sentence Analysis</string>
    <string name="annotated">Annotated Dictionary</string>
    <string name="rhymes">Rhymes</string>
    <string name="offline">Offline Dictionary</string>

    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="dictionary_error">Encountered an error when trying to load dictionary!</string>


    <string name="notice_text">
        Reykunyutsyìp is an UNOFFICIAL Android client of Reykunyu. It is made by Kip, this is not affiliated with Reykunyu. \n
        If you encountered any problems with the APP, please report it here: https://github.com/KipJM/ReykunyuAndroid/issues , and not to Reykunyu \n
        I hope you enjoy the app!
    </string>

    <string name="appinfo_text">kaltxì!
        This is an unofficial Android client of Reykunyu, the Na\'vi dictionary made by Wllìm. This app is created by Kip! \n
        \n
        This app is open-source and licensed under the BSD 2-Clause "Simplified" License (https://github.com/KipJM/ReykunyuAndroid/blob/master/LICENSE). \n
        You can find the app\'s source code and builds on its github: https://github.com/KipJM/ReykunyuAndroid . This is probably where you got the app! \n
        \n
        <u>If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the app, please reach me on Github: <b>@KipJM</b> or Discord: <b>@kipppppppp</b></u> \n
        \n
        Huge thanks to Wllìm for creating Reykunyu, and his help in creating this app! \n
        btw, here\'s a completely unaffiliated ad to Kelutral if you want more resource to learning Na\'vi: https://kelutral.org
    </string>

    <string name="credits_text">
        This app downloads information from Reykunyu (https://reykunyu.lu) (https://github.com/Willem3141/navi-reykunyu). \n
        This app does not contain any dictionary or translation data on it\'s own, they\'re all downloaded and then displayed in app. \n
        \n
        \n
        The online translation search data is downloaded during search, then processed and displayed in app. Aside from the query and search language, no other data is sent. \n
        For the offline dictionary, it is downloaded and cached onto the device, where it\'s processed and searched on-device. However, the audio and image data are still downloaded from Reykunyu during runtime. \n
        The app features real-time search suggestions, the contents in the search box will be automatically sent to Reykunyu, in order to receive the suggestion data. The type of data sent is the same as the online search. \n
        \n
        \n
        The logos (icon and banner) of Reykunyutsyìp are made by me (Kip). Not to be confused with the logos of Reykunyu.
        <i>(Reykunyu data credits)</i> \n
        <b>Dictionary data</b> \n
        The offline dictionary cache data is licensed under CC-BY-SA-NC 3.0(https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/3.0/). This excludes the Annotated Dictionary data, the audio files, and the animal drawings—these are copyrighted by their respective authors. \n
        The base dictionary data was taken from Eana Eltu by Mark Miller, Tirea Aean, and others, and then edited further by Eana Unil, Tekre, and Wllìm. The Annotated Dictionary definitions were taken from the Annotated Dictionary project by Plumps. \n
        \n
        <b>Audio</b> \n
        The voice clips were provided by Plumps (who recorded them for dict-na\'vi(https://dict-navi.com)) and tsyili (who recorded them for Learn Na\'vi(https://learnnavi.org/navi-vocabulary/)). \n
        \n
        <b>Artwork</b> \n
        The drawings of Pandoran animals were made by Eana Unil. (Haven’t encountered one yet? Try searching for [toruk]!).
    </string>

</resources>
